&gt；&gt；演讲者1：所以领导整个讨论，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: So leading this entire discussion,
我们一直在说我们想知道我们的类型。
we've been saying that we want to know our types.
我们想要使用一种编码风格，使我们的类型更加明显。
We want to use a coding style that makes our types more obvious.
到目前为止，我只使用了我们所知道的JavaScript来做这件事。
And up to this point I've been using only what we know about JavaScript to do that.
我一直在建议我们可以限制可以进来的价值观的种类
I've been suggesting that we can restrict the kinds of values that can come in for
例如，类型比较。
type comparisons, for example.
我认为这是一个有效的
And I think that is a valid and
值得的方法，将提高您的代码质量。
worthwhile approach that will improve the quality of your code.
不管你是喜欢还是
Regardless of whether you like or
不喜欢目前的趋势，这些打字系统，如打字稿和流动。
dislike the current trend towards these typing systems like TypeScript and Flow.
我要说的是更广泛的类别，类型感知衬里。
And I'm gonna say in a broader category, type-aware linting.
正如我们前面所说的，衬里本质上是一种工具，它适用于以下几个方面的观点
As we said earlier, linting is essentially a tool that applies an opinion about
你的代码和给你的意见，以便你可以决定，你知道吗？
your code and gives you that opinion so that you can decide, you know what?
我同意我不应该那样做。
I agree I shouldn't do that.
我的短裤捕捉到了所有我不想做的事情，而且
My linter catches all kinds of things that I don't wanna do, and
我很高兴我的林特抓住了它。
I'm glad my linter catches it.
我非常赞成衬里的想法。
I'm very much pro the idea of linting.
就像我说的，我只支持可配置的链接，
As I said, I'm only pro linting that is configurable,
然而，因为没有一个大小适合所有人。
however, because there is not a one size fits all.
现在，我不像你们中的许多人那样处于这样的情况下，你们是在一个团队中。
Now, I'm not in the situation like many of you are, where you're on a team.
但即使是在做这个决定的时候，
But even with respect to making that decision,
您应该仍然能够让团队以民主的方式做出决定。
you should still be able to have the team decide democratically.
而不是团队只能挑选
Rather than the team only be able to pick
世界上所有其他团队都做过的事情。
what every other team in the entire world has done.
更好的是团队可以决定什么对他们有效，并且
It's still better that the team could decide what works for them, and
团队中的个别成员对这是什么有发言权。
that the individual members of the team get to have a say-so in what that is.
我们称之为风格指导。
We call that style guidance.
这是个古老的学期。
That's an old school term.
您的团队需要一个风格指南，并且
Your team needs a style guide, and
每个人都应该在风格指南中投票。
everybody should have a vote in the style guide.
我不喜欢和团队一起工作，还有一些
I don't like it when I go and work with a team, and there's some
团队中的仁慈的独裁者为每个人做了所有的决定。
benevolent dictator on the team that has made all the decisions for everybody.
人们在休息的时候来找我
And people come up to me during the breaks and
他们就像我害怕尝试这个因为他会拒绝我的请求。
they're like I'm scared to try this cuz he's gonna reject my pull request.
这不是一个健康的文化。
That's not a healthy culture.
每个人都应该对你的团队有发言权，而不是我。
Everybody should get a say-so in what works for your team, not me.
你和你的团队成员应该说。
You and your team members should get to say.
&GT；&GT；演讲者1：所以广义地说，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: So broadly speaking,
我经常遇到这样的问题：你对打字稿有什么看法？
I get a lot of times this question of what do you think about TypeScript??
嗯，我对打字稿的看法和我对流程的看法是相似的，
Well, what I think about TypeScript and what I think about Flow are similar,
我很高兴它们的存在，即使我不使用它们。
which is I'm glad that they exist even though I don't use them.
我不使用打字稿，也不使用流程，我曾经告诉人们
I don't use TypeScript and I don't use Flow, and I used to tell people
我不这么做的原因是因为他们解决了我没有的问题。
the reason I don't do that is because they solve problems that I don't have.
我现在对此有不同的看法，
I have a different perspective on that now,
一种最近发展起来的观点。
a perspective that has evolved recently.
这并不是说我不使用它们是因为我没有
It is not the case that I don't use them because I don't have
他们解决的同样的问题，这不是恰当的说法。
the same problems that they solve, that's not the appropriate way to say it.
我不用那些工具或者不喜欢那些工具，
I don't use those tools or don't prefer those tools,
因为他们修复问题的方式让我的代码变得更糟。
because they're fixing the problems in a way that I think makes my code worse.
问题是存在的，正如我在我们讨论的这个单元中一遍又一遍地说过的，
Problems exist, as I have said over and over again in this unit of our discussion,
如果您正在编写代码，而对类型一无所知，那么这就是一个问题。
it is a problem if you are coding and not knowing anything about your types.
这是一个问题，我们应该解决这个问题。
That is a problem and we should solve that problem.
只是我对如何解决这个问题有不同的看法，你和我一起吗？
It's just that I have a different opinion on how to solve it, you with me?
所以在我和你讨论解决方案之前，
So before I talk to you about a solution,
让我们看看TypeScript和Flow可以为我们做些什么。
let's look at what TypeScript and Flow can do for us.
一般说来，它们的好处是什么？
What are their benefits, broadly speaking?
我明白这是一个非常精简的论点，
I understand that this is a very sort of reduced argument,
有一个更加复杂和生动的生态系统。
there is a much more complex and vivid ecosystem.
我的意思不是以任何方式来谈论这些，有一个完整的课程
And I don't mean in any way to talk down about these, there's a whole course on
前端大师，甚至可能不止一个，关于打字脚本。
Frontend Masters, or maybe even more than one, about TypeScript.
这些都是伟大的工具，背后有神奇的、聪明的人。
These are great tools with fantastic, intelligent people behind them.
但从广义上讲，它们在生态系统中处于什么位置？
But just sort of broadly speaking, where do they fit within the ecosystem?
他们会为我们做什么？
What are they gonna do for us?
好的，第一，他们会发现与类型相关的错误，
Well, number one, they're gonna catch type-related mistakes,
这是件好事。
that's a good thing.
我们需要帮助发现与类型相关的错误。
We need help catching our type-related mistakes.
我希望有一个工具能够理解我想用类型做什么，并且
I would like to have a tool that understood what I wanna do with types, and
帮我找出我什么时候做错了。
helped me figure out when I didn't do that correctly.
那会让我成为一个更好的程序员。
That would make me a better coder.
第二，它们确实传达了类型意图，因为类型在代码中。
Number two, they do communicate type intent, because the typing is in the code.
当然，他们有模式，他们只做推理。
Course they have modes where they are doing only inference.
但本质上，打字稿的最大卖点是
But essentially, the big selling point of TypeScript and
流程是您可以将这些类型批注直接分层在代码的顶部。
Flow is that you can layer these type annotations directly on top of the code.
在某些方面，你这么做的最大原因之一是因为
And in some respects, one of the biggest reasons why you do that is because
它会让你的代码更明显。
it's gonna make your code more obvious.
嗯，我可以清楚地看到这个东西是一个整数，
Well, I can clearly see that that thing is an integer,
或者那东西是一根绳子，对吧？
or that thing is a string, right?
那很好。
That's good.
第三，我认为这一点经常被忽视，但是
Number three, and I think this is often overlooked, but
也许是最大的事情之一。
maybe one of the biggest things.
是通过这样做，
Is that by doing so,
通过选择加入这个系统，你会得到一个惊人的数量
by choosing to opt into that system, you get an amazing amount
通过工具生态系统可以直接显示在您的ID中的反馈。
of feedback through the tooling ecosystem that can show up live directly in your ID.
太棒了，我看过一些自动完成的
It's awesome, I've seen some of the auto completing and
像TypeScript这样的东西所做的即时推论和类型分析。
on the fly inferences and type analysis that something like TypeScript does.
在这一点上，TypeScript比Flow要好得多，但是
TypeScript does it a lot better than Flow at this point, but
我相信流量会赶上的，对吧？
I'm sure Flow will catch up, right?
我认为IDE与TypeScript集成
I think IDE integration with TypeScript
比我见过的任何集成在IDE中的项目都要好，这太棒了。
is better than any project that I've ever seen integrated in an IDE, it's fantastic.
我碰巧没有使用IDE。
I happened to not use IDEs.
所以我碰巧没有从中受益，但是
So I happened to not benefit from any of that, but
这并不意味着我不尊重它，我认为它太棒了。
that doesn't mean I don't respect it, I think it's fantastic.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：这些工具有一些注意事项。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: There are some caveats to these tools.
第一，你所依赖的推理
Number one, the inferencing that you rely upon, which you
当你有一个不打算注释的地方时，就依赖于推理。
rely upon inferencing whenever you have a place where you're not gonna annotate.
[笑]你所依赖的推理真的只是一个最好的猜测。
[LAUGH] The inferencing that you rely on really is just a best guess.
不是坚如磐石。
It's not rock solid.
我们在编译时尽可能多地猜测一些东西。
We're guessing something as much as we can at compile time.
我们真的不知道在运行时会发生什么。
We don't really know what's actually gonna happen at run time.
实际上，这是从第二个开始的，因为注释是可选的。
That flows from number two actually, because the annotations are optional.
这意味着您团队中的开发人员，如果他们不在
Which means the developers on your team, if they don't put an annotation on
变量typescript将默认为any类型，除非您将其关闭。
a variable, TypeScript will default to the any type unless you have that turned off.
它将默认为ANY类型，然后您将无法从中获得任何好处。
It will default to the any type and then you're not getting any benefit out of it.
所以它是一个选择加入的系统。
So it is an opt-in system.
如果你不选择一个特定的地方，你只能得到最好的猜测。
And if you don't opt in in a particular place you're only getting a best guess.
它可能会导致一种错误的安全感，如果你
It can lead to a false sense of security if you're
对你的用法不是很小心。
not being very careful about your usage of it.
&gt；&gt；演讲者1：这来源于我一直在说的话。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: This flows from really what I've been saying the whole time.
任何未键入的地方，无论是在您的代码中还是在您的代码中
That any place that isn't typed, either in your code or
您的代码涉及的内容不在您的应用程序中。
things that your code touches that are not in your application.
如果没有打字，就会有不确定性。
If they aren't typed there is uncertainty.